<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>writeup on Jacob Shin</title>
    <link>/tags/writeup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writeup on Jacob Shin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jacob Shin</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:06:36 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/writeup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: Solved in a Flash</title>
      <link>/posts/ractf-solved-in-a-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:06:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ractf-solved-in-a-flash/</guid>
      <description>Use strings to look for strings in the flash.bin file. Use grep to look for strings with &amp;ldquo;ractf&amp;rdquo; in it.
$ strings flash.bin | grep ractf ractf{Fl4shDump5Ar3VeryFun!!} </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: Return of the EmojASM</title>
      <link>/posts/ractf-return-of-the-emojiasm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 21:01:15 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ractf-return-of-the-emojiasm/</guid>
      <description>It looks like we have another EmojiASM problem! Note: Depending on what editor/browser you view this on, the emoji&amp;rsquo;s might not be shown properly. That means copying and pasting the emojis might not work well. Try using a browser.
Problem Description Impressive work. But the emojasm gods have provided you with one more foul challenge. Once again, the web interface should be above.
Info from the EmojiASM Webpage Architecture  General-purpose registers X and Y (both 8 bits wide) Accumulator Register A (8 bits wide) 3x Tape Drives, T0 T1 and T2 (descibed below), each with the following:  1 input buffer register (TnI) 1 ouput buffer register (TnO) 1 write flag (TnW)   Obviously each tape drive has a position on the tape as well, which changes as the tape gets moved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF Writeup: Babybof1 Pt2</title>
      <link>/posts/castorsctf-babybof1pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2020 20:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/castorsctf-babybof1pt2/</guid>
      <description>The Problem Description: Ghidra Decompilation: As we can see from the above decompilation, the vulnerability in the program is gets().
The call to gets() doesn&amp;rsquo;t check to make sure our input will fit into the buffer we give it,
so we can write past the length of the buffer, leading to a classic buffer overflow vulnerability.
The gets() means we the input can contain any character, even \x00, except for newlines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>